Finding Aid for the Will Ella Tatom Johnson Smith and James Mapheus Smith Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- J. M. S. -- Writings - Manuscripts - Articles
  - Writings -- Manuscript -- Social Psychology Chapter VIII (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Writings -- Manuscript -- Social Psychology Chapter IX (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Writings -- Manuscript -- Social Psychology Chapter X (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Writings -- Manuscript -- Social Psychology Chapter XI (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Writings -- Manuscript -- Social Psychology Chapter XII (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Writings -- Manuscript -- Social Psychology Chapter XIII (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Writings -- Manuscript -- Social Psychology Chapter XIV (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Writings -- Manuscript -- Social Psychology Chapter XV (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Writings -- Manuscript -- Social Psychology Chapter XVI (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Writings -- Manuscript -- Social Psychology Chapter XVII (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Writings -- Manuscript -- Chapters 13 & 14 (Unidentified) (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Writings - Publication -- “Six Boys in Trouble” (Box 13, Folder 12)
- J. M. S. --Writings - Masters Thesis -Articles
  - Writings -Masters Thesis “A Sociological Analysis of Six Typical Cases of Problem Boys (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Writings -PhD. Dissertation “A Study of the Behavior of Institutional Children in an Unsupervised Play Situation” (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Writings --Articles -"The Agreement of Observers Concerning Groups of Behavior Traits” (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Writings - Article - “The Agreement of Three Observers After Practice in Simultaneous Recording of Behavior” (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Writings -- Article -- “Analysis of Mediate Action Tendencies” (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Writings - Article - “An Approach to the Study of the Social Act” (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Writings -- Article -- “Approach to a Systematic Social Psychology” (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Writings -- Article -- “Attempted Explanation for the Decadence of Societies” (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Writings -- Article -- “Attitude Homogeneity and Length of Group Association” (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Writings - Article - “Attitudes Towards War and Capital Punishment as to Size of Community” (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Writings -- Article -- “Behaviorism vs. Heredity" (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Writings -- Article -- “Brief for a Sociological Research Journal” (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Writings -- Article -- “Change of Attitude Toward the Law” (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Writings -- Article --"Change of Attitude Toward Punishment of Criminals” (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Writings - Article -- “Change of Attitude with Reference to Birth Control” (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Writings - Article -- “Chronological Sequence of Events in the Operation of the Steel Industry by the Secretary of Commerce” (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Writings - Article - “Circulation of Daily Newspapers, 1935” (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Writings - Article - “Circulation of Farm Magazines” (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Writings - Article - “Circulation of National Magazines, 1935” (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Writings - Article - “Classification of Eminent Men” (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Writings - Article - “Communicative Act” (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Writings - Article - “Comparison of White and Indian Students Toward the Negro” (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Writings - Article -"Concordance in Change of Attitude with Reference to War and Capital Punishment” (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Writings -- Article -- “Concerning the Magnitude of the Behavior Sample for the Study of Behavior Traits in Children” (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Writings - Article -- “Control Interaction” (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Writings - Article -- “The Differential Impact of Selective Service Inductions on Occupation in the U. S.” (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Writings - Article - “Differential Minimum Standards of Training in Social Research: Discussion” (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Writings -- Article -- “Distance Gradients in Psychological Phenomena” (Box 14, Folder 29)
- J. M. S. --Writings - Articles
  - Writings - Article - “Dominance as a Cultural Concept” (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Writings - Article -- “Degrees of Social Intimacy” (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Writings -- Article -- “Effects of Some Conditions of Rating Occupational Prestige Upon the Agreement of Raters” (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Writings -- Article -- “Eminent Men” (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Writings -- Article -- “Empirical Scale of Prestige Status of Occupations” (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Writings - Article - “An Estimate of the Center of the Relief Population of the U. S. (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Writings -- Article --"Ethnocentrism Must Be Destroyed” (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Writings - Article - “An Examination of Some of A. G. Sundbarg’s Hypotheses of Age Distribution of Population with Special Reference to the U.S.” (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Writings - Article - “An Experiment to Test the Reliability of Estimates of Use of Time” (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Writings -- Article --"Farewell the Horse” (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Writings -- Article --"Freedom From Want Requires Population Limitations” (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Writings - Article - “General Formal Education by Field of Eminence” (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Writings - Article - “General Formal Education of Eminent Men” (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Writings - Article - “The Genius as Leader and Person” (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Writings - Article -- “The Greatest Common Component in Science” (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Writings -- Article --"Group Centered Behavior” (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Writings - Article - “Group Judgments in the Field of Personality Traits” (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Writings - Article - “Hypothesis vs. Problem in Scientific Investigations” (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Writings - Article - “Imitation and Suggestion Re-Examined” (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Writings - Article - “Intelligence of University Students by Size of Community of Residence” (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Writings -- Article --"Interpretation on Genius” (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Writings -- Article --"Is America Educating for Peace” (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Writings -- Article --"Is New York to be Another Home?” (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Writings -- Article --"It May Not Be Long Now” (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Writings -- Article --"Jewish Production of American Leaders” (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Writings -- Article --"Leadership; The Management of Social Differentials” (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Writings -- Article --"Library Service and Efficiency Gradients in Missouri (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Writings - Article - “Malignant Neoplasm Defects Among Selective Service Registrants” (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Writings - Article - “A Method of Analyzing the interaction of Children” (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Writing - Article -- “The Method of Elimination in Scientific Study” (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Writings - Article -- “Mobility of American Congressmen” (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Writings - Article - “The Mobility of Eminent Men” (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Writings - Article - “Mobility Patterns of Urban Strangers” (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Writings - Article - “National Origins of Prominent Americans” (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Writings - Article - “National Origins of Prominent Immigrants” (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Writings -- Article --"New Course for College” (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Writings - Article - “A Note on Attitude Among Protagonists of War and Capital Punishment” (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Writings -- Article --"Note on the Longevity of Prominent Americans” (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Writings - Article - “A Note on Pavlov’s Conception of the Unconditioned Response (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Writings - Article - “A Note on the Progressive Generalizations of Data” (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Writings - Article - “A Note on Stability in Questionnaire Response” (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Writings -- Article --"Observational Behavior” (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Writings - Article - “Occupational Differentials in Physical Status” (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Writings - Article - “Occupational Mobility of Notable Persons” (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Writings - Article - “On the Increase in Homogeneity of Attitudes During a Sociology Class” (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Writings - Article - “On the Increase in Homogeneity of Attitudes During a Sociology Class -Second Report” (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Writings - Article - “Personal Dominance and Leadership” (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Writings -- Article --"Population Characteristics Associated with Relief Intensity” (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Writings - Article - “Populational Characteristics of American Servicemen in World War II” (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Writings -- Article --"Possibility, Probability, Certainty” (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Writings - Article - “A Preliminary Experiment in Predicting Success and Failure in Military Service of Men Previously Rejected for Neuropsychiatric Reasons” (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Writings - Article - “A Preliminary Report on Judgments of Personality Traits From Observational Records” (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Writings - Article - “A Preliminary Report on Judgments of Personality Traits from Observational Records” (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Writings - Article - “Proposals for Making a Scale of status of Occupations” (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - Writings - Article - “Psychological Foundations of Situational Sociology” (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Writings - Article - “The Psychology of the Corporate Act” (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - Writings - Article - “Racial Origins of Eminent Persons” (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - Writings - Article - “Re -employment Statistics Bulletin, No. 1 (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - Writings - Article - “Re-employment Statistics Bulletin, No. 2 (Box 15, Folder 60)
- J. M. S. --Writings -Articles-Writings by Others
  - Writings -- Article -- “Regional Distribution of Eminent Americans With Especial Reference to the SouthWest” (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Writings -- Article -- “Relief Intensity Gradients” (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Writings - Article - “A Research Note on Homogamy of Marriage Partners in Selected Physical Characteristics” (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Writings - Article - “A Revised Behavioristic Approach to Social Psychology” (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Writings - Article - “Rural and Urban Origins of Members of the American Congress” (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Writings - Article - “A Second Report on Changes in Attitude Toward the Negro” (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Writings -- Article -- “Should Knowledge of Contraceptives Be Disseminated?” (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Writings - Article - “Similarities of Marriage Partners in Intelligence” (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Writings - Article - “Social Interaction and Collective Behavior” (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Writings - Article - “Social Situation, Social Behavior, and Social Group” (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Writings - Article - “Some Factors in Friendship Selections of High School Students” (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Writings - Article - “Some Political Characteristics of American Congressmen, 1800-1919” (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Writings -- Article -- “Some Relationships Between Intelligence and Geographic Mobility” (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Writings - Article - “Spontaneous Change of Attitude Toward Capital Punishment” (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Writings - Article - “Spontaneous Change in Attitude Toward the War” (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Writings - Article - “A Study of Social Participation and of Leisure time of Leaders and Non-Leaders” (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Writings - Article - “A Study of the Unsupervised Behavior of a Group of Institutional Children” (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Writings - Article -- “Theological School Enrollments 1937-1947, 1947 1950: A Survey of 561 Recognized Theological Schools” (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Writings - Article - “Tier Counties and Delinquency in Kansas” (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Writings - Article - “Trends in the Ages of gainful Workers, by Occupations, 1910-1930” (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Writings -- Article --"Trends Toward Multiple Authorships in Psychology” (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Writings -- Article --"True Function of Government” (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Writings - Article -- “Tuberculosis Among Selective Service Registrants” (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Writings - Article - “University Student Intelligence and Occupation of Father” (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Writings - Article - “The Urban Distribution of Prominent Americans” (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Writings - Article - “An Urban-Rural Intellectual Gradient” (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Writings - Article -- “Veterans Assistance During the Mobilization Period” (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Writings - Article - “War Attitudes in Peace and War” (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Writings -- Article --"Weight-Height Ratio and Personal Ascendancy” (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Writings -- Article --"What are the Characteristics of Reliefers?” (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Writings - Articles - “WPA Research Bulletin -Cases Receiving General Relief in Urban and Rural Areas” (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Writings - Article - “WPA Research Bulletin -Intensity of Relief July 1933-June 1935” (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Writings - Article - “WPA Research Bulletins -Statistics of Youth on Relief” (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Writings -- Report - Note on Selective Migration of American Negroes (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Writings -- Report - Organization Under Decentralized Plan of Operations (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Writings -- Report - “Preliminary Study of Selective Migration of American Negroes” (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Writings -- Report - “Program Interpretation vs. Scientific Analysis” (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Writings -- Report - Selective Migration in Maryland and Virginia, As Revealed by Data on Examination of Selective Service...” (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Writings -- Report - Selective Service Contributions to Knowledge of Rural-Urban Differences in Physical and Mental Status (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Writings -- Report - Selective Service Rejection Rate (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Writings --Chart -- Civilian Occupations of Males Inducted and Enlisted in the US Army and US Navy Through 1945 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Writings -Chart -- Coefficients of Correlation Between Economic, Educational, Moral and Other Social Conditions, and Regional...” (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Writings -- Chart -- Federal Statistical System (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Writings -- Chart -- Foreign Born Eminent American and the Question of Immigration (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Writings - Chart - Mean Prestige ratings of 100 Representative Occupations (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Writings -- Chart -- Negroes In Who’s Who Distribution by Occupational Groups and Separate Occupations (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Writings -- Chart -- Probable Error of Coefficient By Rank Method (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Writings -- Chart -- Rejection Rates Per 100 Selective Service Registrants Physically Examined, By State, 1940-1944 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Writings -- Chart -- University of Kansas: Department of Physical Education (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Writings - By Others -- American Council of Learned Societies (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Writings - By Others -- Barzun, Jacques (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Writings - By Others -- Cannady, Paul A. (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Writings - By Others -- Corbett, Edward L. (Box 16, Folder 51)
- Writings By Others - Class Assignments
  - Writings - By Others -- Dexter, Lewis A. (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Writings -- By Others -- Edwards, Thomas I. (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Writings -- By Others -- Gaumnitz, Walter (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Writings - By Others -- Hailey, O. L., Reverend (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Writings - By Others -- Harper, Alice (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Writings - By Others -- Hart, Hornell (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Writings - By Others -- Howe, Elizabeth (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Writings - By Others -- Howard, George Elliott (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Writings - By Others - Huggins, Margaret (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Writings - By Others -- Lawson, Lois (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Writings - By Others -- Leiter, Russell Graydon (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Writings - By Others -- Logan, E. M. (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Writings - By Others -- Mason, Byron (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Writings - By Others -- McGill, Kenneth H. (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Writings - By Others -- Mitchell, Mildred B. (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Writings - By Others -- Park, Robert E. (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Writings - By Others -- Reuter, E. B. (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Writings - By Others -- Robert, Percy A. (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Writings - By Others -- Visher, Stephen S. (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Writings - By Others -- Wolfkein, Seymour (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Writings - By Others -- Woods, Frederick Adams (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Writings -- Report-Appendixes to Archives Report: Index (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Writings -- Report-"Approaching Decline in the Nation’s Manpower Between 18 and 26 Years of Age” (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Writings -- Report-"Archives of the History of American Psychology-Excerpts from the Annual Report, August 1966-August 1967” (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Writings -- Report-"Cases Receiving General Relief in Urban And Rural Areas July 1933-December 1935” (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Writings -- Report-"Recommendations of the Steering Committee for the Information Systems Study” (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Writings -- Report-"Statistical Advisers to the Manpower Consulting Group” (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Bibliographies-Manpower and Total Systems (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Bibliographies-Spengler on Civil Weakness (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Class Assignment “Allport’s Group Fallacy Concept” (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Class Assignment “Analysis of a Case A Study With Regard T” (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Class Assignment “Bernard’s Definition of Social Psychology” (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Class Assignment “Breakdown of Primary Group Contacts and the Consequent Solutions of Some...” (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Class Assignment “Children Astray” (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Class Assignment “Concept ’Object’” (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Class Assignment “Definition of Culture” (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Class Assignment “Imagination in Animals” (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Class Assignment “Language is acquired” (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Class Assignment “Mead’s Idea of How the Child Becomes an Object to Himself” (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Class Assignment “On Attitudes” (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Class Assignment “On Piaget’s Method in Gathering Material for his Book on Language Responses..” (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Class Assignment “Physical Contacts and Social Contacts” (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Class Assignment “Relation of Language to Thought and Imagination” (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Class Assignment “Relation of Thinking to Imagination” (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Class Assignment “Revery and Day-Dreaming” (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Class Assignment “Rise of Images in Consciousness” (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Class Assignment “Significance of New York” (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Class Assignment “Situational Approach to the Study of Genius” (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Class Assignment “To Be Immortal” (Box 17, Folder 48)
- Writings -Lecture Notes
  - Writings - Lecture Notes January 1927 - February 1928 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Writings - Lecture Notes March 1928 - July 1929 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Writings - Lecture Notes 1925-1930 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Writings - Lecture Notes n.d. (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Writings - Lecture Notes n.d. (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Writings - Notes n.d. (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Newspaper Clippings
  - Newspaper Clippings - Joseph P. Kennedy (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper Clippings - Rose Kennedy (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper Clippings - John F. Kennedy (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper Clippings - John F. Kennedy (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper Clippings - John F. Kennedy (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper Clippings - John F. Kennedy (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper Clippings - John F. Kennedy (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper Clippings - John F. Kennedy (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper Clippings - John F. Kennedy (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper Clippings - John F. Kennedy (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper Clippings - Jacqueline Kennedy Onassis (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper Clippings - Jacqueline Kennedy Onassis (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper Clippings - Jacqueline Kennedy Onassis (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper Clippings - Jacqueline Kennedy Onassis (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Newspaper Clippings - Jacqueline Kennedy Onassis (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper Clippings - John F. Kennedy Jr. & Caroline Kennedy (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Newspaper Clippings - Edward Kennedy (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Newspaper Clippings - Edward Kennedy (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Newspaper Clippings - Edward Kennedy (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Newspaper Clippings - Edward Kennedy (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Newspaper Clippings - Edward Kennedy (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Newspaper Clippings - Joan Kennedy (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Newspaper Clippings
  - Newspaper Clippings Robert F. Kennedy (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper Clippings Robert F. Kennedy (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper Clippings Robert F. Kennedy (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper Clippings David Kennedy (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper Clippings Kathleen Kennedy (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper Clippings Robert F. Kennedy Jr. (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper Clippings Joseph Patrick Kennedy (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper Clippings Lyndon B. Johnson (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper Clippings White House (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper Clippings - White House (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper Clippings - White House (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper Clippings - White House (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper Clippings - Mount Vernon (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Newspaper Clippings - Mount Vernon (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper Clippings - Mount Vernon (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Newspaper Clippings - Mount Vernon (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Newspaper Clippings - Mount Vernon (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Newspaper Clippings - Miscellaneous (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Newspaper Clippings - Miscellaneous (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Newspaper Clippings - Miscellaneous (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Two volumes of World War II Administrative History: Bureau of Aeronautics Summary Typescript, produced with the assistance of James Mapheus Smith
- Oversize Materials
  - Certificates of Appreciation -Willa Smith (2)
    Diplomas -James Mapheus Smith (4)
    Painting -Unidentified
    Scrapbook -Clippings of Washingtonia